<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>KP Learns</title>
    <link>https://kplearns.pages.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on KP Learns</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 02:51:34 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://kplearns.pages.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Commands</title>
      <link>https://kplearns.pages.dev/notes/hugo-commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 02:51:34 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kplearns.pages.dev/notes/hugo-commands/</guid>
      <description>I use Hugo for this website. That doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean I actually know all the commands. These are the basic commands that have been serving me well.&#xA;hugo version Create new website package/folder&#xA;hugo new site newwebsite cd newwebsite Start server locally&#xA;hugo server hugo server -D (for drafts) Add new content&#xA;hugo new content posts/my-first-post.md Publish the site&#xA;hugo After this, the file will be in the public folder&#xA;To clean the public folder for new build: Delete the public folder and rebuild it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Git Commands</title>
      <link>https://kplearns.pages.dev/notes/git-commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 02:30:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kplearns.pages.dev/notes/git-commands/</guid>
      <description>I often find myself forgetting the basic commands for Git. I know it&amp;rsquo;s dumb but it&amp;rsquo;s just easy to keep all of them in one place for reference.&#xA;Also, for anyone new to Git - these are all the commands you need to get started.&#xA;git init # command to convert any folder to a git repo. It creates a .git folder inside and then git tracks the changes made in it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM Basic Terms</title>
      <link>https://kplearns.pages.dev/articles/llm-basic-terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 02:10:04 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kplearns.pages.dev/articles/llm-basic-terms/</guid>
      <description>With AI tools like ChatGPT and Gemini rising, there are a lot of terms floating around us that may be confusing to people. Here&amp;rsquo;s a simple guide:&#xA;Large Language Model (LLM) These AI tools are trained on human languages and thus are called language models. They are called large because they are trained on obscene amount of data. Imagine a large whale opening its mouth with everything going inside. That&amp;rsquo;s LLM with text.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
